Sitting here with my head in my hands
手捧额头 静坐桌前
Ideas that come and go
想法似云烟
Sketching my heart out, nothing will turn out
绞尽脑汁 一无所获
Everything seems so-so
作品却不顺眼
I've been here before, and I know that I can
相似的一幕 彷佛昨天
Do it if I try
刚刚跨过的挑战
But why, oh, why
为何 为何
Do you stumble before you fly?
逆境总是难避免
My wheels keep turnin'
我脚步向前
My fire's still burnin'
我激情无限
'Cause right now I'm learnin'
我牢记经验
How to get to the other side
只为来到灵感彼岸
It's a game of waitin'
我不怕等待
Anticipatin'
我笃定信念
But I keep creatin'
我愈战愈坚
So I can get to the other, get to the other side
只为了来到灵感彼岸呀 来到灵感彼岸
Get to the other side
来到灵感彼岸
So I can get to the other, get to the other...
只为了来到灵感彼岸呀 来到灵感彼...
Keep on believin', I'll be achievin'
相信自己 咬紧牙关
The harder that I go
梦想会实现
Don't really know how, I won't give up now
路途遥远 勇往直前
Until I steal the show
但我会最耀眼
With time, it gets better, I'll be a trendsetter
我将引领 潮流前线
Doin' it my own way
是我的夙愿
Won't stop 'til I seize the day
来定义时尚圈
My wheels keep turnin'
我脚步向前
My fire's still burnin'
我激情无限
'Cause right now I'm learnin'
我牢记经验
How to get to the other side
只为来到灵感彼岸
It's a game of waitin'
我不怕等待
Anticipatin'
我笃定信念
But I keep creatin'
我愈战愈坚
So I can get to the other, get to the other side
只为了来到灵感彼岸呀 来到灵感彼岸
Get to the other side
来到灵感彼岸
So I can get to the other, get to the other side
只为了来到灵感彼岸呀 来到灵感彼岸